Guide to the International Brigades Archive, Moscow: Selected Images ALBA.PHOTO.177
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Folder 191: 15th International Brigade Volunteers, Group Shots, Many Unidentified, 1937-1938
  - [Men and woman group shot, small pennant with "F.U.E" on it], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191125)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/125
  - Group from 15 International Brigade Auto Park, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191126)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/126
  - Emporium [men exercise on board a ship], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191127)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/127
  - Jose Maria Sastre and Dave Doran [looking at a book], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191128)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/128
  - [Small group shot, man standing in center has his arm in a sling, hill in background], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191129)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/129
  - [Two men with a mule in front of a car], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191130)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/130
  - Cuban Company (Tarazona), 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191131)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/131
  - [Very large, crowded group shot], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191132)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/132
  - 15th International Brigade Intendencia, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191133)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/133
  - [Very large, crowded group shot], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191134)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/134
  - [Two soldiers in conversation], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191135)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/135
  - [Two soldiers talking, one with eye patch], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191136)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/136
  - [Seated group shot with officers, women], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191137)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/137
  - [Men sitting around a table, one reading], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191138)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/138
  - [Conversation in front of a truck], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191139)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/139
  - [Closeup group of soldiers], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191140)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/140
  - [Two men, one sitting in a chair, badly blurred], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191141)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/141
  - [Large group shot, men and women], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191142)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/142
  - [Six-man group shot, soldiers in helmets with rifles, cart and horse in background], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191143)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/143
  - [Two men, one with leather jacket and cap, in front of buildings], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191144)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/144
  - [Soldiers carrying lumber (?)], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191145)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/145
  - [Crowd of men gathered for address], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191146)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/146
  - [Two men talking in front of a door], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191147)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/147
  - [Group shot men and women in town], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191148)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/148
  - [Group shot troops with artillery gun], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191150)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/150
  - [Group shot, one seated man to left reading newspaper], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191151)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/151
  - [Troops and officers posed with two artillery guns], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191152)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/152
  - Fan Film, [circular photo-montage of portraits of individual soldiers], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191153)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/153
  - [Men, women in town with flag], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191154)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/154
  - [Group of men outdoors, some sitting on stone wall], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191155)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/155
  - [The British Anti-Tank Battery, with Commander Hugh Slate (in cap and jacket standing in the middle of the second row; to his immediate left is second-in-command Jeffries Mildwater.], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191159)
    Moscow Number: 5/191/159
  - [Group of seven soldiers], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 177_191160)
- Folder 192: 15th International Brigade Sports Contests and Football Team
  - [Ball game or race?], undated (Box 2, Folder 18, Item 177_192002)
    Moscow Number: 5/192/2
  - [View from the sidelines, of a ball game or race?], undated (Box 2, Folder 18, Item 177_192003)
    Moscow Number: 5/192/3
  - Anglo-Americans Playing Football, undated (Box 2, Folder 18, Item 177_192004)
    Moscow Number: 5/192/4
  - [Football team group shot], undated (Box 2, Folder 18, Item 177_192005)
    Moscow Number: 5/192/5
  - [American Football players in a huddle], undated (Box 2, Folder 18, Item 177_192006)
    Moscow Number: 5/192/6
  - [Play along the line of scrimmage], undated (Box 2, Folder 18, Item 177_192007)
    Moscow Number: 5/192/7
  - [The winners celebrate, holding flower bouquets], undated (Box 2, Folder 18, Item 177_192008)
    Moscow Number: 5/192/8
  - [A football huddle], undated (Box 2, Folder 18, Item 177_192009)
    Moscow Number: 5/192/9
  - [Large group shot women present victory bouquets], undated (Box 2, Folder 18, Item 177_192010)
    Moscow Number: 5/192/10
  - [Team pose in football uniforms], undated (Box 2, Folder 18, Item 177_192011)
    Moscow Number: 5/192/11
  - [Other team pose in football uniforms], undated (Box 2, Folder 18, Item 177_192012)
    Moscow Number: 5/192/12
  - [Football/soccer team pose in uniforms], undated (Box 2, Folder 18, Item 177_192013)
    Moscow Number: 5/192/13
- Folder 193: 15th International Brigade Band and Musicians, 1938
  - 15th International Brigade Band, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 19, Item 177_193001)
    Moscow Number: 5/193/1
  - 15th International Brigade Band, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 19, Item 177_193002)
    Moscow Number: 5/193/2
  - 15th International Brigade Band, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 19, Item 177_193003)
    Moscow Number: 5/193/3
  - Ping-Pong Tournament (Jarama), 1938 (Box 2, Folder 19, Item 177_193004)
    Moscow Number: 5/193/4
- Folder 194: Representatives of the Socialist Workers International, Women's, Youth and Labor Organizations of Spain with Commanders and Soldiers of 15th International Brigade, 1938-1938
  - Workers of Forja Show Support for American Battalion, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 20, Item 177_194001)
    Moscow Number: 5/194/1
  - Midday Meal at Activist Congress, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 20, Item 177_194002)
    Moscow Number: 5/194/2
  - [Soldier wearing helmet walks back towards line of troops], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 20, Item 177_194003)
    Moscow Number: 5/194/3
  - Unión General de Trabajadores (U.G.T.) and Confederación Nacional del Trabajo (C.N.T.) Delegates at Activist Congress, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 20, Item 177_194005)
    Moscow Number: 5/194/5
  - [Troops in front of large doorway with banner above it (unreadable)], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 20, Item 177_194006)
    Moscow Number: 5/194/6
  - U.G.T. and C.N.T. Delegates Visit 15th International Brigade (Zapadores), 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 20, Item 177_194007)
    Moscow Number: 5/194/7
  - Cabo School, [soldiers standing in field, long shot], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 20, Item 177_194008)
    Moscow Number: 5/194/8
  - Cabo School, [men seated in classroom with instructors], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 20, Item 177_194009)
    Moscow Number: 5/194/9
  - 15th International Brigade Soldiers Assisting Peasants in Vineyards, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 20, Item 177_194010)
    Moscow Number: 5/194/10
  - Delegation [group photo, man with dog at front], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 20, Item 177_194011)
    Moscow Number: 5/194/11
  - [Banquet hall], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 20, Item 177_194012)
    Moscow Number: 5/194/12
  - Commissars' School during Study, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 20, Item 177_194015)
    Moscow Number: 5/194/15
  - [Crowded dining hall (?)], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 20, Item 177_194016)
    Moscow Number: 5/194/16
  - [Speech being given in an auditorium], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 20, Item 177_194017)
    Moscow Number: 5/194/17
  - [Discussion/presentation on the auditorium floor], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 20, Item 177_194018)
    Moscow Number: 5/194/18
  - [Discussion/presentation on the auditorium floor], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 20, Item 177_194019)
    Moscow Number: 5/194/19
  - [Auditorium stage with banners], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 20, Item 177_194020)
    Moscow Number: 5/194/20
  - [The crowd in their seats], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 20, Item 177_194021)
    Moscow Number: 5/194/21
  - [Flags hung from balconies in assembly hall], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 20, Item 177_194022)
    Moscow Number: 5/194/22
  - [Men gathering straw], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 20, Item 177_194023)
    Moscow Number: 5/194/23
  - [Men gathering straw], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 20, Item 177_194024)
    Moscow Number: 5/194/24
  - [Men gathering straw], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 20, Item 177_194025)
    Moscow Number: 5/194/25
  - [Group pose, straw gatherers], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 20, Item 177_194026)
    Moscow Number: 5/194/26
  - [Group pose, straw gatherers], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 20, Item 177_194027)
    Moscow Number: 5/194/27
  - [Men gathering straw], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 20, Item 177_194028)
    Moscow Number: 5/194/28
  - [Men eating and talking under a tree], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 20, Item 177_194030)
    Moscow Number: 5/194/30
  - De Brouckere in Madrigueras at Parade of the American Battalion [soldiers and civilians standing around], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 20, Item 177_194031)
    Moscow Number: 5/194/31
  - Julius Deutsch in Madrigueras at Parade of the American Battalion [officer at attention], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 20, Item 177_194033)
    Moscow Number: 5/194/33
  - Youth Delegation Visiting 15th International Brigade [men and women talking under a tree], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 20, Item 177_194034)
    Moscow Number: 5/194/34
  - De Brouckere in Madrigueras at Parade of the American Battalion, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 20, Item 177_194035)
    Moscow Number: 5/194/35
  - Youth Delegation Visiting 15th International Brigade [group of men and women with soldiers], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 20, Item 177_194036)
    Moscow Number: 5/194/36
  - [Women in conversation, children beside them], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 20, Item 177_194037)
    Moscow Number: 5/194/37
  - [Labor organization assembly], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 20, Item 177_194038)
    Moscow Number: 5/194/38
  - (Left) E. Shinwell, M.P., Former Minister of Mines; (Center) Swaffer of Daily Herald; (Right) T. Williams, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 20, Item 177_194039)
    Moscow Number: 5/194/39
  - [Crowd at labor assembly], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 20, Item 177_194040)
    Moscow Number: 5/194/40
  - Commissar's School Groups; Commander Jose Veneto and Member of Division Milicia de Cultura, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 20, Item 177_194042)
    Moscow Number: 5/194/42
- Folder 195: U.S. Military Attaché with Spanish Republican Army, and Langston Hughes and Earl Browder with 15th International Brigade, 1937-1938
  - U.S. Military Attaché Addresses 15th International Brigade at Quinto, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 21, Item 177_195003)
    Moscow Number: 5/195/3
  - (Left) Colonel Steven O. Fuqua; (Center) Dave Doran; (Right) Hans Amlie at Fuentes de Ebro [Duplicate of ALBA Photo 11-350], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 21, Item 177_195004)
    Moscow Number: 5/195/4
  - [(Left) Col. Steven O. Fuqua; (Center) Dave Doran], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 21, Item 177_195005)
    Moscow Number: 5/195/5
  - (Left) Colonel Steven O. Fuqua, Colonel Copic at Quinto, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 21, Item 177_195006)
    Moscow Number: 5/195/6
  - (Front-Left) Colonel Steven O. Fuqua; (Front-Right) Colonel Copic; (Rear-Left) Robert Merriman; (Rear-Right) Dave Doran at Quinto, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 21, Item 177_195008)
    Moscow Number: 5/195/8
  - (Left) Captain Dunbar; (Center) Robert Merriman; (Right) Colonel Steven O. Fuqua at Brigade Headquarters, Quinto, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 21, Item 177_195010)
    Moscow Number: 5/195/10
  - Group With Earl Browder in Tarazona, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 21, Item 177_195012)
    Moscow Number: 5/195/12
  - Robert Merriman and N. Corman, French Correspondent and Novelist [mounted on caption card, in Russian], Oct 1937 (Box 2, Folder 21, Item 177_195013)
    Moscow Number: 5/195/13
  - Earl Browder Visit [gathered crowd] [mounted on caption card, in Russian], Oct 1937 (Box 2, Folder 21, Item 177_195014)
    Moscow Number: 5/195/14
  - Rose Freed, medical technician, with Langston Hughes, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 21, Item 177_195015)
    Moscow Number: 5/195/15
- Folder 196: Album of 15th International Brigade Photographed by Yugoslavian Volunteer, Major Vladimir Stefanovich (None Identified), Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937
  - [Wide shot men, horses along riverbank], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196001)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/1
  - [Men herding cattle], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196002)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/2
  - [River with trees along the bank], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196003)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/3
  - [Open field, trees near horizon], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196004)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/4
  - [Barren land, buildings visible on horizon], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196005)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/5
  - [Open field, some trees], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196006)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/6
  - [High shot open countryside, road], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196007)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/7
  - [Hilly/mountainous terrain], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196008)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/8
  - [Open fields], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196009)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/9
  - [Soldiers marching in city], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196010)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/10
  - [Soldiers march with flag], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196011)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/11
  - [Officer, men together with Spanish flag], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196012)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/12
  - [Troops talking to each other], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196013)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/13
  - [Men standing together, smoking], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196014)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/14
  - [Four men pose on a sidewalk], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196015)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/15
  - [Horses pulling a large wagon], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196016)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/16
  - [Horses pulling a cart], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196017)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/17
  - [Horses grazing], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196018)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/18
  - [Shirtless men in a trench], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196019)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/19
  - [Soldier in trench with long rifle], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196020)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/20
  - [Soldiers in trench, one aiming a rifle], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196021)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/21
  - [Effigy/dummy in trench with soldiers], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196022)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/22
  - [Soldier in a dug-out cave in a trench], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196023)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/23
  - [Soldier in a trench], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196024)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/24
  - [Soldiers manning a machine gun in a trench], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196025)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/25
  - [Soldiers manning a machine gun in a trench], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196026)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/26
  - [Four troops pose in front of tent, sandbags], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196027)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/27
  - [Four troops pose on a stone wall], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196028)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/28
  - [Three officers pose], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196029)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/29
  - [Large group of soldiers with packs], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196030)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/30
  - [Hilly roadside with telephone pole, buildings], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196035)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/35
  - [A bend in the road, fort(?) visible on moutain in background], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196036)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/36
  - [Barn and other buildings near a road], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196037)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/37
  - [Damaged wall in city], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196038)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/38
  - [Three soldiers sitting under a tree], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196039)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/39
  - [Group shot posed in a trench], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196040)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/40
  - [Three men pose with equipment in field, seated at a table in center of group], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196041)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/41
  - [Circles of rocks among brush], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196042)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/42
  - [Soldier poses in trench with trenchcoat, helmet, rifle, smoking cigarette], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196043)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/43
  - [Two men talking in a field near trees], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196044)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/44
  - [Soldier with beret poses in trench], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196045)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/45
  - [Two soldiers (one African-American) sitting near shelter opening], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196046)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/46
  - [Soldier in front of sandbag wall], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196047)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/47
  - [Men in trench, cannon (?) covered with sheet in background], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196048)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/48
  - [Man at machine gun post (blurred)], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196049)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/49
  - [Man standing in trench with hands in pockets], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196050)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/50
  - [Two men sitting on a stone wall, countryside in background], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196051)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/51
  - [Two men with berets and glasses sitting in a field], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196052)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/52
  - [Three soldiers pose], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196053)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/53
  - [Small group of men on a hillside], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196054)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/54
  - [Wide shot men working in a field], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196055)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/55
  - [Camp setup, car nearby], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196056)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/56
  - [Open field with small stone piles], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196057)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/57
  - [High shot field with mules, a small shelter], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196058)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/58
  - [Troops pose in a trench], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196059)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/59
  - [Officer among the troops], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196060)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/60
  - [Four men lean against a stone wall], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196061)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/61
  - [Soldier in trenchcoat rests on his rifle], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196062)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/62
  - [Road through the countryside], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196063)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/63
  - [Road with trees along left side], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196064)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/64
  - [Road, mountains in distance], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196065)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/65
  - [Road, mountains in far distance], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196066)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/66
  - [Troops pose in foxhole], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196067)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/67
  - [Man crouched near tree], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196068)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/68
  - [Camp with improvised shelters], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196069)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/69
  - [Men socializing at camp], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196070)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/70
  - [Dug out trench (?) (hard to see)], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196071)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/71
  - [Men sitting on ground near trench], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196072)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/72
  - [Soldier working in trench], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196073)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/73
  - [Soldier sitting next to tent entrance, banner hung up as door], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196074)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/74
  - [Many people loading into and on top of a bus], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196075)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/75
  - [Men riding horses], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196076)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/76
  - [Men riding horses], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196077)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/77
  - [Woman walking through fields carrying a basket on her head], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196078)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/78
  - [Railroad tracks], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196079)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/79
  - [Long, straight road, powerlines on each side], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196080)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/80
  - [Road winding through countryside, with railroad tracks alongside], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196081)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/81
  - [Small buildings visible from road], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196082)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/82
  - [Low stone wall], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196083)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/83
  - [Wide shot livestock grazing], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196084)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/84
  - [Open countryside, rugged mountains in background], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196085)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/85
  - [Rugged countryside], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196086)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/86
  - [High shot open countryside], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196087)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/87
  - [Road along open fields, mountain in distance], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196088)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/88